Do you think we're close?
They're almost
impossible to find.
No one's ever
captured one alive.
I agreed to provide security
for you
because I thought you were
close to finding the spider.
Well, it'll be worth the wait.
Dead specimens show that
the peptides
in the spider's venom, they...
Basically, they supercharge
their cellular structure.
That spider can give
superhuman strength and power,
like Las Arañas.
Las Arañas?
The, uh,
mythical spider people
who run across the treetops
and punish evil men with
their black, poisoned touch?
I like to base my research
in science,
not legends, Mr. Sims.
Those powers are wasted here.
These little spiders
have the potential
to cure hundreds of diseases.
It could...
- Are you okay?
- No.
She's trying her best
to keep me from working.
But I'm not gonna
let her do that.
Not when I'm this close.
Perhaps you should rest.
I don't have time.
Thank you.
For the umbrella.
I found it.
I found the spider.
Oh, my God.
- Isn't she beautiful?
- Wow!
Incredible, isn't it?
Something so small
yet have so much power.
What are you doing?
I don't...
I don't understand.
I've been searching
for that spider for years.
No, don't...
We could help so many people.
I'm not interested
in helping people.
No one helped me
when my family was starving.
My road was not
as clear as yours.
We didn't have
the same choices.
You're making
the wrong decision.
- Give me the spider!
- No.
You're making
the wrong decision.
- Give it to me.
- No.
You can just walk away.
No.
Her journey
will not be easy,
but she is strong.
She will come back
when she needs answers.
And when she does...
I will be here for her.
Come on!
Whoa!
- Move!
- All right! All right!
This is 2-10
with a 42-year-old female.
Code three.
Cassie, I lost the pulse.
I'm starting compressions now.
Ben, what are you even doing
back there?
Oh, you wanna come take over?
I can drive.
She's not going room temp
on my watch.
Come on.
How you doing back there?
You know, last time I was
in a vehicle driven like this,
I was being shot at.
I wouldn't want you
to be homesick for the Army.
Never thought
I'd be this happy
to be back in Queens.
What, you've never
been shot at in Queens?
Shouldn't you be in school?
Who flips off an ambulance?
Jesus.
Kids.
- I'm gonna get roped in.
- You're not.
You're gonna be in
the backyard grilling with us.
Mm-mm. I know how
these things work, Ben.
Oh, do you? How do you know?
I bet you've never even been
to a baby shower.
Because, yeah, I'm careful
not to get roped in.
I'm glad I caught you
before you headed back out.
She's gonna be okay.
Who?
Your, uh, patient.
Her little boy
wanted to say thank you.
Um... You know what,
Mr. Ben Parker here
did all the work, so...
Just take it.
Take it.
- That's... I mean...
- Thank you.
- Thanks, buddy.
I'll take you in to see her.
- Are you all immediate family?
- Oh, my God.
I'm her stepdaughter.
I think she might prefer...
Yeah, it's okay, Dad.
I'll see you guys
back at your apartment?
Okay.
Come on, buddy.
Let's go see Mommy.
Okay. This one is
for you. This is for me.
Thanks so much.
What am I supposed
to do with this?
Just put it in your pocket
and then throw it away
somewhere else.
Can't even fold it.
It's like cardboard.
Oh, come on.
We both hate family stuff.
I think I have plans
anyways, so...
Plans?
Since when do you have plans?
You're, like,
impossible to pin down.
Well, I like to keep
my options open.
You know, I might sleep in.
I might go to the museum.
I might walk the dog.
You don't have a dog.
I might adopt one.
Return the favor.
I suspect you were a bit more
of a handful than a puppy.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I was a model foster kid.
I peed outside and everything.
So I, um...
I kinda met someone.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
What's this one's name?
Oh.
Serious.
She's a lucky lady, Ben.
Thank you.
Oh.
"You have
a winning personality."
I guess I got yours
by mistake.
You're an asshole.
Here.
Let's see what your future
holds for you.
What if I don't wanna know?
Well, it's just a cookie.
"You will."
You will what?
- Apparently, I have no future.
- Cassie.
- Do you know what this means?
- What?
It means that their printer
is broken.
We can't eat here anymore.
We'll have it
for you tomorrow.
My dad just needs
to pick up his paycheck.
Well, let me come in
and talk to your dad.
I haven't seen him in a while.
- We can work something out.
- He's not home right now,
actually.
Look, I'll be back tomorrow.
But no more excuses.
I swear. We'll have it.
All right.
Us strays
need to stick together.
Somebody's hungry.
Hope the spiders
were worth it, Mom.
You gotta get, like,
Jaws of Life for that.
MVA, three vehicles.
One vehicle flipped over
with entrapment.
Copy that.
Sending backup
to your location.
It won't open.
All right, sir.
We're gonna get you
out of there, okay?
Just don't move.
Hi, sir.
Can you tell me your name?
Robert.
Robert, I'm Cassie.
I'm gonna
help you out today, okay?
You're gonna be all right.
All right,
I'm gonna cut your seatbelt.
And when I do,
you're gonna fall
and my partner Ben
is gonna help you out
on that side, okay?
Three, two, one.
All right, Robert.
We're gonna move on three.
- Okay? Here we go.
- Yeah.
One, two, three.
Okay.
You're gonna be okay, sir.
Just try and lay still.
We're gonna get you checked...
- Hey! Cassie!
- Ben!
- Cassie!
79 over 55.
Dial it back, I'm fine.
You need a real workup
at a real hospital.
No, you were right.
They're roping ya in.
Games!
You guys are ice-cold.
Cassie!
This place has always
been a death trap.
Are these the shadows
of things that must be
or are they only shadows
of things that might be?
You can't save all three!
...web to be
in more than one place
at the same time.
You are the only one
who can change the future.
No!
Cassie!
That's it, Cassie,
breathe!
Come on!
You're okay. You're okay.
Did I die?
Yeah. You were
down three minutes
before I fished you out.
- Three minutes?
- Yeah.
Welcome back
to the land of the living.
79 over 55.
You need a real workup
at a real hospital
with a real doctor.
I don't need a doctor.
I trust you.
Ah, 80%. No, it's great.
Slightly above that
of a dead fish.
Ah.
All right. Well,
O2 is going up to 89.
Jump back
in the water anytime.
79 over 55.
You need a real workup
at a real hospital
with a real doctor.
Seriously, Ben, dial it back.
I'm fine.
Wait, wait, wait. I need
to get your oxygen levels.
Again?
What are you talking about?
My O2 is 89.
No, it's...
Oh, you're right.
Are you okay?
What the hell happened
down there?
I'm fine.
I just wanna go home
and watch Idol.
Wow.
Great apartment.
Where's my spider?
They took my spider.
Who are you?
No!
Mm, bad dream?
It's not a dream.
I'm gonna be murdered one day.
Oh, wow, that's a buzzkill.
The same three faces.
Every night, the same vision.
It's a curse.
But we all die someday.
Nothing we can
really do to stop that.
But if you saw
who was going to murder you...
you'd try to stop them.
Okay...
You have no idea
of the torment and torture
of dying over and over again.
And I can't escape it.
So I'm not gonna
sit back and let it happen.
I will find them
and kill them first.
So you know who did it...
I mean, will do it?
It's always those three faces.
Can you imagine
how frustrating it's been?
Trying to identify someone
I've only seen in a vision?
Mm-hmm.
But as the years pass,
there have been
technological advances.
New ways to find people,
if you know their faces.
The kind of technology
I've heard
the National Security Agency
has been pursuing.
What are you doing?
How are you poisoning me?
What's your password?
I can't tell you. Oh, please!
Is "please" your password?
Tell me quickly
before the paralysis
reaches your lips
and I'll stop the poison.
Q-9-2-0...
B-3-7-5.
Oh, God.
Believe me, it's a good thing
you had no idea
today was the day
you were going to die.
- Hey, Cassie.
- Hey.
I'm serious. You should
open, like, a barbecue.
- Hey.
- Hey, man.
You know
what you're doing.
- I saw him leave.
- Yeah, I...
- Hey!
- Cassie!
- Hi.
Hey, the next time
you wanna go swimmin',
maybe you should stick
to Astoria Park.
Oh, that's really funny.
You're such a funny guy.
Are you pressing the burgers?
I'm releasin' the fat.
That's called flavor, man.
Plus, it's, like,
really flammable.
- Here you go.
- Oh, thanks.
You don't think that maybe
in light of recent events
I could use a beer?
Well, as you know,
the protocol is
no booze within 24 hours
of your death. So...
- Is that protocol?
- Yeah, it's protocol.
That's boring.
I feel like there's more
of a story there.
No, there's...
You guys, we've seen this
a hundred times.
It was cardiac arrest.
When your heart starts
back up again, you're fine.
Really?
Dead, huh?
Did you see
a white light or...
Well, actually, I saw Jersey,
- so you tell me.
- Oh, come on, you saw Jer...
- Hey.
She hit me with a Jersey joke.
Has he been
pressin' the burgers again?
Yeah, they're ruined now.
For you, sir.
Oh, now they're really ruined.
Oh, okay.
- We're ready to start.
- What?
What?
They're starting,
so you should get in there.
No, you were right,
they're roping ya in.
- Yeah. Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Have fun.
...for you, okay.
Oh, my God.
- Hi.
- Look at you. Hi.
Okay. This is crazy.
Well, I couldn't
decide, so I got two.
Yeah, that's like...
- Hey. Hi.
- Hi.
Um, Cassie Webb.
Um, thanks for having me.
You're Ben's partner.
I'm his sister-in-law, Mary.
- Nice to meet you.
- Mm-hmm.
Ben is so excited
about being an uncle.
I don't know
what we'd do without him.
- Especially with Richard away.
- Again.
Where is it this time?
He's in Mumbai...
Shanghai...
I can't keep track.
Never stops
leaping around in there.
And always hungry.
Um, does it have a name?
The...
We're saving that
for one of the games.
- Games?
- Games!
Games!
Okay.
"My mother always cut
the crusts off my sandwiches."
Oh.
Chloe, is that you?
Yes.
My mom said the crusts
would make my hair go curly.
It was years
before I figured that one out.
Okay.
Whose is this?
Don't give him any money.
Oh, it's mine.
You must have at least
one fond memory
of your mother.
Um, well, my mother actually
died, uh, in childbirth.
Well, but it wasn't that bad.
It wasn't like...
I mean, obviously,
it was bad, you know.
She died.
Um, but, um,
I grew up totally healthy.
Death in childbirth
is super rare.
I mean, she chose to be, like,
way deep in the Amazon
for the last month
of her pregnancy
hundreds of miles away
from any
medical facilities, so...
Okay, so let's, um,
let's move on
to the next game.
Guess the name
of Mary's baby.
Oh, yes!
Okay, I'll kick things off.
- Sam.
- Nope.
Steven.
- He's not named Steven.
- Shoot.
- Baby sausage?
- You guys are ice-cold.
Richard Junior?
Richard wishes.
Get your hamburger.
Cassie,
what's your guess?
Um...
Mm. Hmm...
Do that thing
where you throw it up
and catch it on the...
- Oh, my God.
- Ben?
- Look at that.
- The name is...
Baby sausage?
Richard Junior?
Richard wishes.
Get your hamburger.
Cassie, what's your guess?
Put five dollars down,
let's go.
Wait. We just did this.
Do that thing
where you throw it up
and catch it on the...
What, seriously,
is this part of the game?
Uh, sorry.
They're calling everyone in.
Fire down at the docks.
So...
You okay?
Yeah. I just got
a weird sense of déjà vu.
I got you, man.
Come on,
come on. This way.
Turn around, come on!
Come on.
Go. Go. Go.
Okay, looks like
a fractured left radius.
Otherwise stable.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Check his abdomen.
Okay, and internal injuries.
Good catch.
Let's go. Come on.
Hey, I need
to get my guys in there.
No, it's not safe.
The structure's unstable.
Hey, the people are trapped.
We need to treat 'em
before we move them.
The place is packed
with explosives.
Industrial grade fireworks.
It could blow up any minute.
- Cassie!
- Blow up any minute.
Cassie!
It's not safe.
This place has
always been a death trap.
Come on, come on. This way.
Turn around, come on!
Otherwise stable.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait. Check his abdomen.
And internal injuries.
Good catch.
Let's go. Come on.
I gotta get my guys in there.
The structure's unstable.
Hey, the people are trapped.
Place is packed
with explosives.
Industrial grade fireworks.
This place has
always been a death trap.
Cassie!
Cassie! Cassie.
I need you at the triage.
Sir, you're okay.
You're okay.
He's stable.
Ready to transport.
Copy that.
You're gonna be okay.
Wait. O'Neil!
Hey, what is it? I gotta roll.
Will you let me drive?
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
I just have a weird feeling.
Cassie, I need you over here.
Will you just let me drive?
Look, you had
a bad experience on the job.
I don't think
that's what's happening.
Don't let it
mess with your head.
Cassie, come on!
This is O'Neil.
Clear of dock side.
Headed back...
O'Neil, come on.
Come on. O'Neil.
Come on!
Wake up!
O'Neil, come on.
Did you see
a white light or...
O'Neil, come on.
Cassie! Cassie!
Come on. Come back.
Come on, come on.
- Ben, help me.
- Cassie, Cassie, it's okay.
It's all right. It's okay.
It's okay. Okay?
There's nothing you could
have done. Okay?
So, was it worth the trouble?
The scale
of the NSA surveillance
is unprecedented.
They can access everything.
There's...
There's nowhere to hide.
That's the idea.
The potential is infinite.
It's...
It's intoxicating.
But in the wrong hands,
I mean,
people can be tracked
wherever they go.
It's gonna change everything.
As long as it has the ability
to find those women now
before they get their powers.
This is what they look like
in your visions
as well as you can recollect.
Their faces have been
taunting me for years.
We don't know exactly
when your vision takes place,
so I'm giving us
a 10-year range
just to be safe.
Here's what they should
look like now.
They're younger
than I thought. I...
I didn't know
we'd be targeting teenagers.
They're teenagers now,
but in the future
they have powers,
and they will try
to destroy me.
I came from nothing,
less than nothing.
I will not give up
everything I've built
and have my life cut short.
Well, if they ride
public transportation,
go to a museum,
get money from an ATM,
wherever they are
in the world...
Find them.
I pay you a fortune.
Yeah, I'll find them.
Still no blurriness.
No double vision.
No discoloration at all.
Your eyesight is good,
and all your other vitals
check out.
Um, but what about
the visions?
How am I
seeing that stuff?
Mm, sometimes when
we experience trauma,
it can have a lasting effect.
This isn't trauma.
I knew he was gonna die.
I saw it.
Cassie, I have
all your reports here
from your other consultations.
Your head CT was normal.
Your MRI was clear.
The scan showed
no abnormalities.
I know that it sounds crazy,
I know,
but I don't understand
what's happening.
I will be recommending
that you take a week off.
Get some rest.
Watch old movies.
If you still have concerns,
I can run some bloods
or refer you to psych.
But I'm sure everything
will be back to normal
before you know it.
I am in the presence
of the Spirit of Christmas
Yet-to-Come.
And you're going
to show me shadows of things
that have not yet happened
but will happen.
Spirit of the Future,
I fear you more
than any other specter
I've seen.
But even in my fear,
I must tell you, I am too old.
I cannot change.
Whose funeral
were they talking about?
Hey, Cass,
it's me again. Uh, Ben.
I know you're there.
Just pick up.
Okay, well, uh,
O'Neil's funeral
starts at 2:00
in Poughkeepsie.
Everyone's going.
I know it's the last place
you wanna be,
but it would help Susan
if you came.
It might help you too.
Look, if you leave now,
you can still make it.
Cassie?
Cass?
Before
I draw nearer to that stone,
answer me one question.
Are these the shadows
of things that must be
or are they only shadows
of things that might be?
I hate to break it
to you, Scrooge,
but you can't change anything.
Are these the shadows
of things that must be?
Or are they only shadows
of things that might be?
This isn't
gonna change anything.
Guess you didn't die
after all.
Please keep all personal
belongings with you
throughout your trip.
Come on, guys. This way.
Come on,
let's go down the rail.
Yeah, awesome.
Can I have one
to Poughkeepsie, please?
Anya Corazón is now moving
onto the platform.
She's on her own.
Julia Cornwall is on
the concourse, also alone.
And Martha Franklin.
Shit. Um...
What are the odds
of them all being
in the same place
at the same time?
It's not a coincidence.
There must be
something that connects them.
Or...
something that will.
Please keep all belongings
with you at all times.
If you see
something suspicious,
find a member
of the MTA staff.
Train to New Haven
now ready to leave
on Track 25.
All aboard.
New York City
is a whole new level
of crazy these days.
Train to New Haven
now ready to leave
on Track 25.
All aboard.
Train to New Haven
now ready to leave
on Track 25.
All aboard.
This is the train
to Mount Vernon, right?
Oh, my God.
Train to New Haven
now ready to leave
on Track 25.
- All aboard.
- Is this real?
Are you okay, dear?
Oh, God,
I think I'm going crazy.
New York City
is a whole new level
of crazy these days.
This is the train
to Mount Vernon, right?
I hope not.
The Mount Vernon train
will be leaving in
three minutes, Track 8.
Hey, get back here!
Yeah, they're coming your way.
Get... Get up!
Get off! Get off!
- Get up!
- Me?
Go! Get off! You're gonna die
if you stay here!
- Get up!
- We are?
Are you threatening us?
This is
an emergency situation.
I need you
to follow my instructions.
Get off the train. Come on.
My mom told me never
to talk to strangers. So...
- Get up!
- Hey, give me that back!
Hey, give me that back!
I am so pressing charges.
Okay, knock yourself out.
Give me
my freakin' skateboard back.
Let's go.
What? No.
Okay, never mind. Um...
Give me
my freaking skateboard back.
Okay...
Um, what exactly
is this emergency?
This woman's
trying to abduct us!
What?
No, that's not... That's...
Shh. That's...
That's your emergency. That.
Is anybody else
seeing this?
That man is trying
to kill you.
- And how do you...
- Why?
I don't know. Come on.
We don't have tickets
for this train.
That's your biggest concern?
Please stand
clear of closing doors.
This train is departing.
Please be kind
and remove your bags
from the empty seats
and place them
in the luggage rack above.
Come on.
Okay.
Hey, am I on the right train?
I don't know, man.
Please have all tickets ready.
This is Metro North
to North...
Hey, what are you doing?
No! Help...
Holy shit.
Come on.
Go.
Run!
There's an emergency exit
to the street that way.
Go.
Hey, help. Over here.
I've never been
so happy to see cops.
You guys need
to call for backup.
That will not be necessary
as long as you cooperate.
Wait. What?
No, it's not me. Ow.
No. You don't understand.
- We're being attacked.
- Don't worry. Calm down.
You're safe.
Run! Go!
Run!
Run! Run!
Go! Go! Go!
Come on.
- Get in.
- What?
Here you go.
- Thank you so much.
- Get in!
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Move. Slide over.
I appreciate it.
Thank you so much.
Oh, wow, thank... Hey!
That guy was nuts.
Do you guys think
he killed those cops?
Uh, he could climb on walls
and dodge bullets.
- How is that even possible?
- It's not.
There's not enough
frictional force
in the bare human foot
to overcome gravity
and keep him stuck to the wall
much less the ceiling.
What the hell is going on?
Yeah, well, science
didn't seem to stop him,
so what good is it?
- What good is science?
- Okay, enough.
- Please, don't fight.
- Enough.
No, I was just telling them...
Enough! Your voices
are, like, drilling
in the center of my skull
and I need to think.
I'm Cassie. Okay?
What are your names?
I'm Julia Cornwall.
My dad lives here in New York,
and my mom
lives back in L.A., but...
We don't need
your whole life story.
I'm Anya Corazón.
Mattie Franklin.
- Thank you for protecting us.
- No, no, no.
I'm not... That's not...
That's not
what's happening here.
I'm not protecting you.
I am, I am...
Your parents can handle this.
My parents
are on a business trip.
Uh, yeah. My parents
are out of town too.
Uh, my dad is
busy working, so...
Oh, my God.
I was gonna
go stay with some friends.
Well,
where do your friends live?
I'll drop you off first.
...in
finding a person of interest
seen in the attack
on multiple NYPD officers
at Grand Central Terminal
this afternoon.
That's great. Good.
I hope they find
his crazy ass.
That was insane.
They better lock him up.
Right? I mean...
She is also the same person
police are seeking to question
in the possible abduction
- of the three teenage girls.
- She?
Eyewitnesses have identified
the woman in her early 30s.
The public has been asked for
any information and to keep
- an eye out for these girls.
- Uh... What?
What? That's...
But you guys...
What about them?
And he was crawling
on the ceiling.
What about that guy?
I mean, you saw. I...
No one saw ceiling guy.
Everyone thinks
you're the kidnapper.
Yeah, because you told them
I was.
I didn't know
what was happening.
Okay, guys.
My uncle, Jonah,
can totally help us.
- I'm gonna call him.
- You have a phone?
You know they can
track those nowadays, right?
- Hey! You can't do that.
- She's right.
It's okay. Daddy will buy you
a new one.
What is your problem?
- What do you mean?
- Please.
- I'm just trying to help.
- Okay.
Anyone who wants to leave
can leave right now.
- Okay.
- Wait.
Sorry. No,
you can't actually leave
because you guys
are the only ones
that know
what actually happened.
Okay, well, this is what
we're gonna do, okay?
We're just gonna, like,
lay low for a little bit.
And, um...
I'll figure out
how to get out of this.
This is still
not a kidnapping.
Okay?
Feels like a kidnapping.
How'd they get away?
It's like they knew
I was coming.
No hits at the train station,
bus depot,
or any of the bridges.
Wherever they went,
there aren't any cameras.
The police don't have
this technology.
You have access
to every camera in the city.
We should be ahead of them.
I went to a lot of trouble
to steal you these tools.
Use them better.
I've always wanted
to be a Girl Scout.
Of course you did.
Anybody else starving?
All I have is gum.
Here. I found this
in the glove compartment.
Wait. That bag's
already been opened.
We don't know how long
it's been in there.
Okay, I hope you're good
at, um, catching squirrels.
Okay, so what's the deal
with ceiling guy?
I told you, I don't know.
I've never seen him before.
Then how did you know
he was coming?
Oh, my God.
I'm kind of more interested
in why he's trying to kill us.
I don't know.
Crazy shit's been happening,
and I don't know why.
Stop asking me. Okay?
Wait. You're the paramedic.
You saved my stepmother,
then you were
super awkward about it.
That does sound like me.
Wait. I recognize you too.
What?
Yeah. You live in my building.
You leave your junk mail
in the lobby
and then everybody else
has to clean it up for you.
Okay. Well, there should be
a recycling bin there.
You don't think this is weird?
That we both know you?
It's honestly, like,
the least weird thing
that's happened all day.
What?
Total stranger.
No.
You flipped me off.
That's not really
narrowing it down much.
You guys,
this is so freaky.
Who are you? What is going on?
I can see the future.
Kind of.
I mean...
- Oh.
- What the hell?
See?
She didn't see that coming.
It doesn't work like that.
You guys, just give her
a chance, please.
Wait. When you were
looking into the future
did you see us
in the middle of nowhere
eating
glove-compartment jerky?
Okay, look. Believe me
or don't. I don't care.
I didn't ask
to be doing this with you.
And I didn't ask for this
to happen to me, either.
Also, I'm pretty sure
I saved all of your lives.
So, you're welcome.
How does it work?
It just happens.
Can you do it now?
I can't control it.
You know the other guy can
walk on the ceiling, right?
Uh, no, he can't.
He was using his hands.
Why are you like this?
I'm just saying
it was more of a crawl.
It was like a spider...
person.
I'm gonna be back
in a few hours.
Where are you going?
I need to check
some things out
about all of this.
You can't just leave us here.
We'll be okay, Julia.
- We don't need a babysitter.
- Oh, yeah, sure.
Just three teenagers
alone in the woods.
Definitely not the opening
of a horror film.
You are way safer out here.
Just, you know, be, um,
like a Girl Scout girl.
Be that. Just be that.
Can you bring us
some sandwiches?
Cassie.
Can we trust you?
Three hours. Okay?
Just stay here.
And don't do anything dumb.
Seriously.
Don't do dumb things.
She was talking to you.
Okay, well,
you're just a bitch, so...
I know tae kwon do.
You?
Yeah, I had
a few rough years in school
when my parents
were divorcing.
So I wanted to feel like
I could fight back
if I needed to.
Uh...
That's what I thought.
One second, cat.
Come on.
"Research on
Amazonian spiders,
"peptides, more peptides."
Come on, where is it?
Ah. Spider people.
"Las Arañas."
Have you ever heard
of Las Arañas?
Me neither.
"According to local folklore,
"they possess powers
derived from spider venom
"and are incredibly fast,
incredibly strong
"and they can climb
like spiders."
Just like ceiling guy.
How would you know
if you could climb a wall
if you've never tried?
Okay, let's not mention that
to anybody.
"Las Arañas are said
to possess a sixth sense
"as if they had the ability
to glimpse the future."
Oh, my God.
Hey, who's got the jerky?
You ate it all.
I had, like, three pieces.
- Out of five.
- You counted?
You also ate all mine.
- What's this?
- Stop.
Stop. Just...
Jeez.
Okay, forget jerky.
Did you guys see that diner
like a half-mile
down the road?
Let's just go there
and get real food.
- Cassie told us to stay here.
- Come on, Julia.
She bailed on us.
We don't have any money, genius.
Well, I have money, so...
You have money
so we should do what you want?
You got something to say?
You know,
I bet your dad is a senator
and your mom
sits on the board at the Met.
And you summer in the Hamptons
next to Martha Stewart.
So sad about Martha Stewart.
My parents are in Beijing
where my dad is raking in
a ton of money
for making plastics
that pollute the ocean,
and my mom is spending it
all on hideous art.
So...
I talk to them on Mondays.
So who do you live with?
The housekeeper.
Well, on the upside,
no curfew.
I bet you have
your own room at least.
I live with my dad
and his wife and their kid.
- What about your mom?
- Uh, she's...
not really around.
She bailed on you?
Right. So, diner?
We spend some of Mattie's
daddy's pollution money?
Yay.
I'm going to order
everything on the menu.
Julia, you in?
Hey.
We have to take care
of ourselves.
Yeah.
You're right.
Let's go do this.
She's kind of cute
when she's mad.
I heard that.
You are making
the right decision, Julia.
You will not like me
when I'm hangry.
Who says we like you now?
God! I knew
we shouldn't have done this.
Shit.
Do you think there's ticks?
Can we walk
- a little faster, please?
- Julia.
You said this was a shortcut.
Are we lost?
Do you know
where you're going?
You know
Yeah. Actually, I do.
Ow! Shit!
Okay. Don't talk to anybody
except to order.
We're in the middle
of nowhere.
No one's gonna track us
down here.
Just don't make eye contact.
I hope they have cherry pie.
Let's sit at the bar.
There you go.
Here.
Should we make a game plan?
Eat first, strategize later.
Okay. Here we go.
Mm. Keep it coming.
Let's just eat quickly
and then get out of here.
Absolutely, great idea.
Uh, right after cherry pie.
No. No cherry pie.
Julia, tell me you agree
that we should get dessert.
Yeah, whatever you guys
are arguing about...
I'm sure you're both
making really good points.
Yo, she's looking at you.
We should go over there
and talk to them.
Really?
No. We...
Should we? We can't.
Come on. You know you want to.
No.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
This is not a good idea.
- What're you doing?
- Yeah, what are you doing?
Just hold on a second.
What is this?
It's just
a little confidence boost.
This...
This isn't really my style.
So what? You look cute.
Come on.
This is not a good idea.
Seriously, guys.
Okay.
Hi. Hey, guys.
I'm Mattie. This is Julia.
- Can we sit?
- Yeah, of course.
We've been saving
the seats for you.
Awesome.
Hey, what's up?
How you doing?
Nice to meet you, too.
Thank you
for your information.
Can you just confirm
your location?
4 Star Diner.
Davis Road, Route 206.
- Hey.
- Church Hill.
Possible sighting
in Church Hill, New Jersey.
Connect me with
Church Hill police dispatch.
Yeah. Patching you in now.
2-2-3 dispatch.
On scene at 4 Star Diner.
Route 206 at Davis Road.
Go ahead, 2-2-3.
No need to send backup.
These aren't
our missing persons.
Code four. Repeat.
These are not
our missing persons.
Girls!
Oh, God damn it.
Let's go. Let's go!
Don't even pretend
that you're cooler
than Britney.
I know you know the words.
Come on, get up here.
So much
for not attracting attention.
Can you...
What are you doing?
- What are you...
- What is that?
We have to go.
I'm so sorry.
Get down!
This isn't what you think.
- Get your stuff.
- You left us.
I'm so sorry.
Julia!
Julia, get back!
Come on!
Stop! Mattie!
No.
This track
is going to be huge.
Are you in the zone?
This is Britney Spears.
Let's try that again.
I love this song.
Guys.
Okay, okay, I'm sorry.
I have to dance.
- Come on, Julia.
- Mattie, no!
Great. Okay.
All right, come on.
- Guys.
- Seriously, dude.
Come on.
Come on. Let's go.
Don't even pretend that
you're cooler than Britney.
I know you know the words.
Come on, get up here.
Hey!
Come on.
You're toxic
- I'm slippin' under
- Hey!
Guys. Guys, guys.
We have to go, we have to...
Girls, get in! Get in! Get in!
Leave everything. Run!
Come on,
let's go. Let's go!
Mattie, come on! Hurry!
- Get in!
- I'm so sorry, Cassie.
God!
So much
for not needing a babysitter.
Do you guys think of anybody
but yourselves?
You're so impulsive
and entitled,
and you don't listen!
- We didn't mean to...
- Whatever!
Don't even say anything!
God!
Your futures were almost...
so different.
You're lucky I saw them.
- I'm so sorry.
- Yes.
You should be so sorry.
All of you should be sorry.
God!
Tsk.
Amaria, where did they go?
I'm running checks now.
I don't understand
how they're doing this.
I've got a match on the woman
who's with them.
I'm not interested in her.
Focus on finding those girls.
Cassandra Webb.
Daughter of Constance Webb, deceased.
Did you say, "Webb"?
Uh, yeah. Do you know her?
That's not possible.
Come on.
He's not gonna stop
until he kills us, is he?
I don't know what he wants.
I don't know anything.
But you can see the future.
Can't you stop him
with your visions?
I don't know
how to control them.
It's useless.
Well, we're alive.
Maybe that's a plus.
Is your hand okay?
It's fine.
First thing in the morning,
I'm taking you all home.
Your parents
can deal with this.
No, they can't.
My mom's in a psych ward.
She, um...
She didn't really cope well
after my dad left,
and so,
I got sent to live with him
and his new family
and I don't think
that they want me there.
I wondered
if they missed me if...
if I ran away.
Hmm. So you did.
My parents
aren't around either.
I think they resent how having
a kid messed up their lives.
I don't think they're gonna
fly back from China
to deal with this.
And I really
don't wanna find out, so...
I'm on my own.
Well, fine.
Then you guys can just...
- go to the police.
- No.
My dad got deported
six months ago.
I came home from school,
and he was gone.
What about your mom?
My mom died when I was five.
It's just me and my dad.
Except he never told me
he didn't have his papers.
So, I've just
been living by myself
at our apartment since then.
You're on your own?
I don't need anyone else
to look out for me.
And I don't have
a curfew, either.
So, I can't go to the police.
Okay?
Until I'm 18, I can't exist.
And there's no way
I'm getting deported too.
Or going
into the foster system.
Well,
foster system isn't always
that terrible.
Things didn't turn out
so bad for me.
Right.
Cassie, please help us.
No one survives once enough
poison enters their system.
You won't be so lucky
next time.
Why are you doing this?
I need to stop them
from killing me.
They're not killers.
They're just teenagers.
In the future,
they become much more.
They will destroy me
and everything I've built.
Those girls cannot exist.
How come you get to decide?
Because I'm the one
with the powers.
If you knew what I knew,
you'd do the same thing.
Would I?
If I knew the price to pay
was the lives of three girls?
The only thing I know
is that, in the future,
they also have powers.
The girls? The girls
have powers in the future?
Did you think you could
beat me with your mind?
Your mother underestimated me.
The power of the spider...
Don't make the same mistake.
Tell me where they are!
They don't mean
anything to you.
You could just walk away.
What is this?
Rise and shine.
Okay, so this guy's hands
somehow release
an acute neurotoxin,
and it is painful.
I was lucky.
The longer he holds on to you,
the more poison
gets into your system.
Then what happens?
Then your heart stops.
But you can offset
cardiac arrest with CPR.
So you interlock your hands
like this.
You lock your elbows,
and then you place
the heel of your hand
right on the sternum. Okay?
And then you pump.
And you wanna go,
like, two inches down.
And you wanna keep a rhythm
like a heartbeat. Okay?
You ready?
Okay, begin compressions.
Go. Good.
Okay. And when do I stop?
You don't stop.
If you stop, they die.
- Oh.
- And if you get tired,
then you need somebody
to take over.
- I'm getting kinda tired.
- Okay.
- Anya, get ready to take over.
- Mm-hmm.
But you have to pick up
the exact same rhythm.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- Ready?
- Yep.
And go.
Great. Nice, Mattie.
Not cool.
Julia, you wanna take over?
Okay.
Get ready.
Okay. One, two, three.
Perfect.
Nice job, Anya.
I've never said this before
in my entire life,
but you're a good teacher.
Well, I've been learning
some things, too.
About my mom.
Wait, so you do know this guy.
My mom did. I think.
That's her.
She's really pretty.
So, this is because of you?
All I know is that
she was researching spiders.
In her notebook,
there's some stuff
about a local tribe in Peru
that can do,
like, crazy stuff.
What kind of crazy stuff?
Climb like spiders.
So, is he one of them?
I need more information.
You're leaving.
I have to go and figure out
what is going on.
How?
You have to go to Peru.
I'll be gone a week.
I don't wanna leave them,
but he's out there
looking for them
and they're relying on me,
and I don't know
how else to protect them.
Okay, uh, look,
I'm staying with Mary
for a few weeks
while Richard's out of town.
He won't find them there.
But, Cassie, I...
I can't pretend to understand
what's going on here.
Just be careful, okay?
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Thank you, Ben.
You didn't ask
for any of this.
Okay, well, neither did you.
You have come back
looking for answers.
Back?
I promised your mother
I would be here.
My mom thought
Las Arañas were a myth.
What do you think?
I think she was crazy
for coming here alone.
Mm, she came here
hoping to extract
healing properties
from the spiders.
She thought
she was being protected.
By Ezekiel Sims?
His motives were selfish.
He used your mom to find us.
But, because he stole
the spider
he was cursed.
And he's been trying to outrun
his destiny ever since.
This is where my mom died?
And where you were born.
I don't understand
why she risked my life
to come here.
To see the future clearly,
you have to heal
the wounds of your past.
That sounds like literally
every therapy session
I've ever avoided.
You have to go back
to your beginning
and keep going past that.
There are powers
you don't even know
you're capable of.
Your thread did not start
when you were born.
Do you trust me?
Not really sure at this point
I have a choice.
You could just walk away.
Your thread did not
start when you were born.
They're almost
impossible to find.
She really is trying her best
to keep me from working.
Not when I'm this close.
But I'm not gonna
let her do that.
Why did you hate me so much?
Thank you.
For the umbrella.
Give it to me.
I found it.
I found the spider.
Incredible, isn't it?
Give it to me.
- No, please.
- Give it to me.
You're making
the wrong decision.
- You could just walk away.
- You're making the wrong...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm s...
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Las Arañas could not stand by.
We tried to save you both.
Her journey
will not be easy,
but she is strong.
Your test results came back.
I'm sorry to tell you
that your baby
has myasthenia gravis.
It's a genetic
neuromuscular disorder.
But I don't have
a neuromuscular disorder.
Life expectancy varies.
Do you need a tissue?
No. No. I need a cure.
I'm afraid there is no cure.
Uh, single target
nucleotide intervention.
It's, um, it's experimental,
but there are some
promising leads in the Amazon.
That's why you went there?
For me?
I have to advise you against
traveling in your condition.
I'm sorry, what are you
offering besides tissues?
I know this is hard to accept.
No, no, I am...
I'm unwilling to accept
a diagnosis of helplessness.
And I'm not gonna
teach my daughter to either.
You did it.
I never knew I was sick.
The spider venom
did have healing properties.
I'm so sorry I spent so long
being mad at you.
I always thought my mom
didn't care about me.
Sometimes you must
sacrifice yourself
for those you love.
I was there.
I was in the room...
I was in the room with her.
How did you do that?
You did that.
Now you're starting to see
what you're capable of.
You came here to learn
the truth about your past.
But you will leave ready
to embrace your future.
Seeing into the future
is no match for Ezekiel.
I need to stop him
before he kills those girls.
But I can't do what he can do.
I can't do the leapy, crawly,
like, death poison.
You didn't get the gift
of the greater
physical strength
or the ability
to release poison,
but seeing into the future
is only the start.
Your mind
has infinite potential.
If you master your power,
you can use the web
to be in more than one place
at the same time.
You are the only one
who can change the future.
And when you take on
the responsibility,
great power will come.
Every day that goes by,
my appointment with death
gets closer.
And you still
have found nothing?
How can she have kept
three teenagers
hidden for a week?
I'm running checks
every three minutes,
scanning CCTV camera.
I have hacked police
and emergency services
frequencies.
I have eyes
on all of their houses,
including friends and family.
Still nothing.
Do you understand?
Huh?
Those girls cannot exist.
They will try to destroy me,
as I will you
if you don't find them.
She can't hide them forever.
Okay, it's still pretty quiet
out there. Uh...
- What'd I miss?
- Ben said words.
- Oh, boring.
- Okay, let's try and remember
- to pick up after ourselves.
- Nice nails.
- Okay, guys?
- Thank you.
- Hey!
- I mean, this is really...
- Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Rude!
- Guys?
- All right, throwing popcorn
- is super fun.
- I cannot wait for that.
- But I also think...
- Guys, either I peed myself
or my water broke.
Ew!
Well, honestly,
you probably peed yourself
because that isn't
supposed to happen yet.
Richard's not here,
and the baby isn't due
for four weeks.
I don't think the baby
got the memo, Ben.
- Okay.
- Okay. Okay. Uh...
Looks like we may have to wait
a little while for the...
...ambulance.
The baby is not waiting.
He's coming now.
Now.
Uh, like, here?
In the dining room?
If Ben doesn't get me
to the hospital, then yes.
Okay. Uh...
Uh, get in the car.
Keep your head down.
It's gonna be okay.
Okay. Um...
Okay, okay.
Everyone okay?
Okay, seat belts, everybody.
Seriously?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
Uh, never mind.
All right, let's step on it.
I might have something.
I've intercepted a call
to the hospital.
St. Timothy's.
Track the route.
Tracking.
The baby is not waiting.
...doesn't get me
to the hospital, then...
No!
Get out, get out, get out!
- Go, go, go!
- No, no!
Shit!
Sorry, guys.
Hey!
Thank you.
So, the last one was
three minutes and 24 seconds
after the previous one.
Uh, uh...
So that means
the time between contractions
is reducing at a rate of...
21.6 seconds.
Oh, that's pretty fast.
You better hurry up
'cause I'm not sticking around
- if it gets gross.
- Okay.
He's heading southwest
on Vernon Avenue.
I'll cut them off
at the Second Avenue
intersection.
Drive faster.
Let's go. Let's go, please.
Hack into traffic control.
Turn the lights green.
Amaria, now.
Turning all
traffic lights to green.
Why is no one stopping? Hey!
Ben, watch out!
- What's happening?
- They're not stopping.
Whoa, whoa!
Ben!
Everyone okay?
Yeah.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I'm fine.
Um...
What is that?
Oh, my God, it's him.
Guys.
Ben, go, go!
Everybody,
get out right now!
Go, go, go!
Cassie!
Get out. Go on.
Get in the ambulance. Go.
It's not over. Go.
Ben, I need you to get Mary
as far away from us
as possible.
Okay? Ezekiel,
he won't care about you now.
Well, what about you?
I liked it better
when you didn't make plans.
You're showing off.
Not yet.
Uh, I think we lost him.
Get in the back
and charge the AED.
- For what?
- Just do it. Go.
Okay, press "charge."
Am I having a heart attack?
I think I'm having
a heart attack.
You're not gonna have
Hey! Hey!
Okay, get ready.
Get it close to the ceiling.
Nobody touch the sides
or anything.
- Ready?
- Okay. Yep, yep.
Wait. Wait.
Now!
Sorry.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Now you're showing off.
Maybe a little.
Now what?
Those girls cannot exist.
- ...doesn't look safe!
- It's a deathtrap.
Infinite potential.
This place has always
been a death trap.
...packed with explosives.
Get down!
Go! Run!
Jump!
Come on,
get in the helicopter.
I have a code 30. PD-36-307.
Requesting airlift support.
Dockside, Queens.
Copy that.
Okay.
It's gonna get a little crazy.
It's already crazy.
You didn't bail on us.
Whatever happens, I promise
I'm going to protect you guys.
We'll protect each other.
We're in this together.
Right?
Yeah.
Okay. We are still
not doing a high five.
I know. It's not cool.
Let's go. Out the back.
- What?
- Go, go, go.
This doesn't look safe.
Well, it's full of explosives
and it's structurally unsound.
That doesn't sound safe.
It's a death trap.
And that's a good thing?
As long as we're not the ones
who get trapped.
No matter what happens,
we need to work together, okay?
We're listening
this time, Cassie.
Yeah, and we won't
be impulsive.
Are we ready?
We have to get to the roof.
He's gonna be here any minute.
Here. Take these.
Put them in as many crates
as you can.
Okay?
You two, go that way.
We need to slow him down.
- Mattie, this way.
- You come with me.
Come on.
I got this one.
Come on, Julia. Let's go.
Anya, go.
Go.
Go straight ahead.
When I say "now," get down.
What do you mean?
It's a dead end.
Now!
Whoa, whoa!
Go! Run!
Now you're really showing off.
Come on, upstairs.
I knew it.
I knew she had a plan.
- Hey!
- We're here!
Down here!
- Here!
- Hey! Here!
Make your way
to the south side.
Come on.
Wait. Get down!
Let's go.
He said south side.
We can go this way.
Anya, stop!
- Let's go!
- Mattie!
Whoa!
We need to go this way.
Come on, Anya. Get down!
Go to the ladder. Let's go.
Come on, come on!
Use the web.
Cassie!
Get to the helicopter.
- Hey!
- Wait! Girls! Get down!
It's not safe to land.
You'll have to get higher.
Guys, this way.
We can get to the chopper
from up there.
Anya, jump.
Jump now! Julia, get back!
Julia, get down!
Oh, God!
You should have walked away!
You can't protect them.
Cassie!
Over here, asshole.
Mattie!
Don't hurt her!
Anya!
Cassie!
You can't save all three.
And when you take on
the responsibility,
great power will come.
Julia, I got you.
Come on.
Mattie. You're gonna be okay.
Anya. Anya, give me your hand.
You still can't beat me
with your mind.
What makes you so sure?
Come on. Come on, come on.
You're just like your mother.
Yes, I am.
You've been trying
to change your future.
But the girls
were never your future.
I was.
No!
No. Cassie!
She's not breathing.
- Her heart's not beating.
- We know what to do.
Beginning compressions.
Interlock your fingers.
Come back, Cassie.
Come on, Cassie, come on!
Keep going. We don't stop.
Come on, Cassie.
I'm getting a little tired.
Okay, okay. I'm right here.
Cassie, wake up! Please.
- Cassie!
- Come back, Cassie.
We're here, Cassie.
We're not leaving you.
Cassie, you got this.
Please. I need you. Please.
Oh, my God!
Cassie.
- It's okay.
- It's okay. It's okay, Cassie.
Oh, my God. We did it.
We did it.
Hey.
Hello.
Oh, he's perfect.
He is.
- He's perfect.
- Yeah.
We're still here, Cassie.
Yeah. We're not leaving you.
I wouldn't be here
if it weren't
for the three of you.
Right back at ya.
Ben said to tell you that
the baby is doing really well.
And he's loving
being an uncle.
Yeah.
All the fun and none
of the responsibility.
That's what he thinks.
Are you all immediate family?
Yes.
They're all mine.
Can we get you anything?
No.
I have everything
I need right here.
No.
You left your junk mail
downstairs again.
And we got takeout.
But we didn't know...
Kung Pao chicken
is perfect.
How'd you know?
Bless you, Anya.
What?
Thank you.
Mattie!
What? I told you I'm starving.
And I told you guys
that you wouldn't...
...wouldn't like you
if you were hangry.
Well, you wouldn't, so...
How's your eyesight?
I can see better
than I ever have.
Oh, yeah?
Can you see us in the future?
Yes.
I can see you.
Standing up
for what you believe.
Let go!
Just give me the bag, lady!
Never giving up.
Discovering you were always
more powerful
than you thought.
Nothing I didn't already know.
I don't know about you two,
but that totally
makes sense to me.
What? I'm serious.
Wow.
What? I'm being serious.
Oh, wow. Okay.
Wow. I was trying to have
a nice bonding moment.
Hey! No, wait. I don't
want to miss the whole...
And now
you're gonna get the...
Whatever the future holds...
we'll be ready.
And you know the best thing
about the future?
It hasn't happened yet.